{
  "id": "flashcard-time",
  "title": "Time",
  "description": "Luyện tập từ vựng: Phút & Giờ.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "1分",
      "answer": "1 phút",
      "speak": "ippun"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "2分",
      "answer": "2 phút",
      "speak": "nifun"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "3分",
      "answer": "3 phút",
      "speak": "sanpun"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "4分",
      "answer": "4 phút",
      "speak": "yonpun"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "5分",
      "answer": "5 phút",
      "speak": "gofun"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "6分",
      "answer": "6 phút",
      "speak": "roppun"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "7分",
      "answer": "7 phút",
      "speak": "nanafun"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "8分",
      "answer": "8 phút",
      "speak": "happun"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "9分",
      "answer": "9 phút",
      "speak": "kyuufun"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "10分",
      "answer": "10 phút",
      "speak": "juppun"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "11分",
      "answer": "11 phút",
      "speak": "juuippun"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "1時間",
      "answer": "1 tiếng",
      "speak": "ichijikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "2時間",
      "answer": "2 tiếng",
      "speak": "nijikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "3時間",
      "answer": "3 tiếng",
      "speak": "sanjikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "4時間",
      "answer": "4 tiếng",
      "speak": "yojikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "5時間",
      "answer": "5 tiếng",
      "speak": "gojikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "6時間",
      "answer": "6 tiếng",
      "speak": "rokujikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "7時間",
      "answer": "7 tiếng",
      "speak": "nanajikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "8時間",
      "answer": "8 tiếng",
      "speak": "hachijikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "9時間",
      "answer": "9 tiếng",
      "speak": "kyuujikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "10時間",
      "answer": "10 tiếng",
      "speak": "juujikan"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "11時間",
      "answer": "11 tiếng",
      "speak": "juuichijikan"
    }
  ]
}